

LISANDRO BIGI

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

PROFILE

Hello! I'm from Córdoba, Argentina, and I'm a Front End Developer (Full Stack in and training) Anthropologist. I have knowledge and experience in: HTML5 | CSS3 | JavaScript | Git | Node.js | Vue.js | React | Angular | PHP | Laravel | Wordpress. Also I have an advanced English level. I'm interested in Web Development, Responsive or Adaptive Web Design, User Interfaces (UI), User Experience (UX), Front-end, Web3 and Web Design.

CONTACT

+54 9 351 631 9690

bigilisandro@mail.com

Córdoba, Argentina

SKILLS

JavaScript	• • • •
HTML CSS	• • • •
React.js	• • • •
Vue.js	• • • •
Git	• • • •
English	• • • •

EXPERIENCE

INCLUIT, React Developer

JUN 2022 - PRESENT

Currently working for iDocket company in the development of a UCMS software platform. Using ReactJS for the front-end development.

PENGYI LABS, Front-end Developer

JUN 2020 - JUL 2022

I worked as a Front-end developer for a software company with projects in Vue and React for clients all around the world.

KICKSTA, Front-end Developer

OCT 2020 - NOV 2021

I worked for this US company in their own main product Kicksta and in their others web applications such as InfluenceGrid and Wedding Hashers.

EDUCATION

EDUCATIONIT, Blockchain Ethereum Solidity

MAY 2022 - AGO 2022

CODERHOUSE, React.is

FEB 2020 - JUN 2020

ACAMICA, Full Stack Web Development

NOV 2019 - JUN 2020

CODERHOUSE, UX/UI Design

MAY 2020 - SEP 2020

FFyH - UNC, Anthropology Degree

FEB 2013 - MAR 2020

CODERHOUSE. Web Designer

OCT 2019 - DIC 2019

